Guide to the Sheila Lukins Papers 1945-2009 (Bulk 1980-2000) MSS 281
© 2010 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Media, 1983-1999
  - Subseries B: Published Media, 1985-1997
    - The Silver Palate Good Times Live VHS Tapes, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      Format: Videocassettes
    - The New Basics Electronic Cookbook CD-ROM, 1990, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      Format: CD-ROMs
    - Sheila Lukins All Around the World Recipe Collection CD-ROM 1 of 2, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Sheila Lukins All Around the World Recipe Collection CD-ROM 2 of 2, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Subseries C: Television and Promotional Appearances, 1983-1999
    Subseries comprises promotional videocassettes and videocassettes of Lukins's television appearances.
    - Morning Break w/Carol WDVM-TV Wash. DC 1983 "Good Times" PR (SL/JR) Choc. Amaretto Mousee; L'Invorno pasta; Pizza Napoli; Potatoes Fontecchio; Minty pea salad (Box 7, Media ID: 218.0001)
    - Morning Break WDVM-TV, Wash. DC, June 28, 1985; Silver Palate (SL/JR) (Box 7, Media ID: 218.0002)
    - Parade Promo Video c. 1986 SL/JR (Box 7, Media ID: 218.0003)
    - Good Morning Bay Area c. 1988 Parade PR SL/JR Strawberry souffle (Box 7, Media ID: 218.0004)
    - Sheila Lukins on "Sonya"/CNN April 19, 1988 (Box 7, Media ID: 218.0005)
    - Sunday Today NBC-TV 11/26/89; Sheila Lukins w/Al Roker (20 second spot in segment on Peter Kamp Cooking School), 11/26/1989 (Box 7, Media ID: 218.0006)
    - Sheila Lukins 1) Sunday Today NBC 11/26/89; 2) 1997 Promotional Highlights, 11/26/1989, 1997 (Box 7, Media ID: 218.0007)
    - Hour Magazine w/ Gary Collins Valentines Day 1990? SL/JR Couer a la creme, with poppyseed framboise (fr. "Good Times"), [February 14, 1990] (Box 7, Media ID: 218.0008)
    - "The Power of Parade", April 23, 1991 SL/JR (Box 7, Media ID: 218.0009)
    - Home Show ABC-TV Oct./Nov. 1991 "The New Basics" S.Lukins Spanish Olives, October-November 1991 (Box 7, Media ID: 218.0010)
    - Good Morning America w/Chantal ABC-TV, 12/91 S. Lukins Olives; Tapenade; hors d'oeuvres; Tortilla pizzas; Potted shrimp, 12/1991 (Box 7, Media ID: 218.0011)
    - 2nd Annual James Beard Awards; Hall of Fame 1992 (Box 7, Media ID: 218.0012)
    - 4/26/94 GMA Return AATW; Good Morning America Comeback! 4/26/94, 4/26/1994 (Box 7, Media ID: 218.0013)
    - QVC May 5, 1994 (Box 7, Media ID: 218.0014)
    - WABC, New York Views, May 21, 1994 (Box 7, Media ID: 218.0015)
    - AMNW Portland 5/25/1994 Sheila Lukins (Box 7, Media ID: 218.0016)
    - Parade "America's Town Hall" PR May, 1994 Sheila Lukins (Box 7, Media ID: 218.0017)
    - Mike and Maty Show--AATW Tour PR, June 1, 1994 Banana Bliss (Box 7, Media ID: 218.0018)
    - The Food Network w/Valerie Harper 6/4/1994 (Box 7, Media ID: 218.0019)
    - Working Woman 8/94 (rough cut) Sheila Lukins Corn Chowder, 9/1994 (Box 7, Media ID: 218.0020)
    - Sheila Lukins 1997 Promotional Highlights (Box 7, Media ID: 218.0021)
    - March of Dimes Charity Auction Tampa Convention Center 10/26/9--Sheila Lukins 30 second spot on local news, 10/26/[1999] (Box 7, Media ID: 218.0022)
    - 09549 #1 Joan Nathan, undated (Box 7, Media ID: 218.0026)
    - 09549 #2 Joan Nathan, undated (Box 7, Media ID: 218.0027)
    - Haven Show #40, undated (Box 7, Media ID: 218.0023)
    - Pittsburgh's Talking WTAE-TV Holiday Cooking, S. Lukins "The New Basics", undated (Box 7, Media ID: 218.0024)
    - Saks Fifth Avenue Silver Palate, undated (Box 7, Media ID: 218.0028)
    - Simon & Schuster--"Good Times Live" Promo (repeating video), undated (Box 7, Media ID: 218.0025)
    - United Airlines "Baby" UAPF-7306, undated (Box 7, Media ID: 218.0029)
    - WABC New York News 2nd copy, undated (Box 7, Media ID: 218.0030)
- Series IV: Magazines
  Series comprises issues of Parade magazine as well as other magazines, some of which include some mention of Lukins, her cookbooks, or the Silver Palate.
  The material in this series is described at the box level.
  - Subseries A: Parade (Box 10)
    Subseries comprises issues of Parade magazine that include Lukins's contributions.
    - Parade (Box 9)
  - Subseries B: Other Magazines
    Subseries comprises issues miscellaneous periodicals, some of which include some mention of Lukins, her cookbooks, or the Silver Palate.
    - Other Magazines (Box 10)
- Series V: Objects, undated
  Series comprises objects from the collection.
  - The Silver Palate Button, undated (Box 11, Object ID: 281.2.0001)
  - The Silver Palate Paper Bag, undated (Box 11, Object ID: 281.2.0002)
  - The Silver Palate Chopsticks, undated (Box 11, Object ID: 281.2.0003)
  - The Silver Palate Tissue Paper, undated (Box 11, Object ID: 281.2.0004)
  - "Capri L'isola dei Sogni" Plastic Bag, undated (Box 11, Object ID: 281.2.0005)
  - "Spago the American Wine and Food Festival" Apron, undated (Box 11, Object ID: 281.2.0006)
  - Blue Apron, undated (Box 11, Object ID: 281.2.0007)
  - Sheila Lukins Campari Chef's Double-breated Jacket, undated (Box 11, Object ID: 281.2.0008)
  - The Silver Palate Cookbook Apron, undated (Box 11, Object ID: 281.2.0009)
  - Sheila Lukins Chef's Double-breated Jacket, undated (Box 11, Object ID: 281.2.0010)
  - The Silver Palate Good Times 10th Birthday Satin Varsity Jacket, undated (Box 11, Object ID: 281.2.0011)
- Oversize Series I: Professional Files, 1945, 1980-1982, 2009
  - Oversize Subseries A: Parade Files, undated
    - Parade Research, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Oversize Subseries C: The Silver Palate, undated
    - The Silver Palate [Japanese] Menu, undated (Map-case 4.A)
  - Oversize Subseries D: Cookbook Files, undated
    - Sheila Lukins "Celebrate" Posterboard, undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Oversize Subseries E: Miscellaneous Menus and Recipes, undated
    - Menus, undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Recipes, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Oversize Subseries F: Press, undated
    - Clippings, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Clippings, undated (Box 13)
    - Clippings, undated (Box 14)
    - All Around the Work Cookbook Advertisement, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Scrap Book Pages, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - News Clippings, undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Oversize Subseries G: Miscellaneous Professional Files, 1945, 1980-1982, 2009
    - Loose Binder Materials, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Muppets Poster, undated (Map-case 4.A)
    - Kitchen Floorplans, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Oversized, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Parade Cover, June 30, 1945 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Posters, undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Signed Grand Chefs of the West Posterboard, undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - "The Silver Palate News", 1980-1982 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Toast to the Children Award, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 12)